# Changes to this value could result in the plugin not loading or your config being corrupted.
version: 1.0

options:
  case-sensitive-answers: true
  interval: 300000
  timeout: 60000
  min-players: 2

#######################################################################################################################################
## Reactions
## If you want to suggest a chat reaction type, or need to ask for help, you can do so in our Discord: https://discord.gg/GGCk3zdgQP
##
## For Unscramble and Type reactions, the answer is used as the question.
## The only difference is that `unscramble` answers are automatically scrambled before being sent in chat.
## For instance, 'Enderman' would become along the lines of 'mnaEdnre', however it won't always be exactly that.
##
## Valid Types (as of 1.0): [UNSCRAMBLE, TYPE, SOLVE]
#######################################################################################################################################
reactions:
  solve_two_pow_8:
    type: "solve"
    question: "2‚Å∏"
    answer: '256'
    reward: 'random'
  threefourfivesix:
    type: "solve"
    question: "34+56"
    answer: '90'
    reward: 'random'
  seventwoeightnine:
    type: "solve"
    question: "72+89"
    answer: '161'
    reward: 'random'
  fourfiveseveneight:
    type: "solve"
    question: "45+78"
    answer: '123'
    reward: 'random'
  sixsixeightseven:
    type: "solve"
    question: "66+87"
    answer: '153'
    reward: 'random'
  nineonefiveeight:
    type: "solve"
    question: "91+58"
    answer: '149'
    reward: 'random'
  type_monster:
    type: "type"
    question: "Monster"
    answer: "Monster"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_enderman:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Enderman"
    answer: "Enderman"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_blue:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Blue"
    answer: "Blue"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_endermite:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Endermite"
    answer: "Endermite"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_blaze:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Blaze"
    answer: "Blaze"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_dragon:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Dragon"
    answer: "Dragon"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_amethyst:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Amethyst"
    answer: "Amethyst"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_diamond:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Diamond"
    answer: "Diamond"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_iron:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Iron"
    answer: "Iron"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_Cactus:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Cactus"
    answer: "Cactus"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_flower:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Flower"
    answer: "Flower"
    reward: 'random'
  type_wheat:
    type: "type"
    question: "Wheat"
    answer: "Wheat"
    reward: 'random'
  type_Axolotl:
    type: "type"
    question: "Axolotl"
    answer: "Axolotl"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_gold:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Gold"
    answer: "Gold"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_mojang:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Mojang"
    answer: "Mojang"
    reward: 'random'
  unscramble_minecraft:
    type: "unscramble"
    question: "Minecraft"
    answer: "Minecraft"
    reward: 'random'
  solve_58_plus_342:
    type: "solve"
    question: "58+342"
    answer: '400'
    reward: 'random'
  solve_76_plus_129:
    type: "solve"
    question: "76+129"
    answer: '205'
    reward: 'random'
  solve_91_plus_507:
    type: "solve"
    question: "91+507"
    answer: '598'
    reward: 'random'

#################################################################################################################################################
## Rewards
## These are the possible rewards a player can get for winning a chat reaction
## If you want to randomly set what reward the player gets (which then uses the chance value), set the 'reward' key in the reaction to 'random'
## Otherwise, set it to the key of the reward, for example 'one_diamond' or 'eight_oak_logs'
#################################################################################################################################################
rewards:
  one_diamond:
    display_name: "One Diamond"
    chance: 10.5
    commands:
      - 'give {player} diamond 1'
  eight_oak_logs:
    display_name: "8 Oak Logs"
    chance: 30.5
    commands:
      - 'give {player} oak_log 8'
  twenty_xp:
    display_name: "20 XP"
    chance: 59
    commands:
      - 'minecraft:xp add {player} 20'